<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Tech news &#8211; Future Code Tech</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 03:58:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Black Hole Image Is Beautiful and Profound, but It Doesn&#8217;t Tell Us Much</title>
		<link>./../../../black-hole-image-is-beautiful-and-profound-but-it-doesnt-tell-us-much/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../black-hole-image-is-beautiful-and-profound-but-it-doesnt-tell-us-much/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sirazkhan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 02:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Tech news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=704</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The first image of a black hole was just released, and it&#8217;s being celebrated around the world as a triumph of science and more evidence of the great march of human progress. In everything being said, there are overtones of the moon landing: &#8220;One small step for man, one giant leap for mankind.&#8221; All of &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="./../../../black-hole-image-is-beautiful-and-profound-but-it-doesnt-tell-us-much/index.html"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Black Hole Image Is Beautiful and Profound, but It Doesn&#8217;t Tell Us Much</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The first image of a black hole was just released, and it&#8217;s being celebrated around the world as a triumph of science and more evidence of the great march of human progress. In everything being said, there are overtones of the moon landing: &#8220;One small step for man, one giant leap for mankind.&#8221;</p>



<p>All of which makes sense. It&#8217;s a significant&nbsp;<a href="https://gadgets.ndtv.com/science/news/black-hole-image-event-horizon-telescope-m87-revealed-images-pictures-2021062">event</a>. The brilliant scientific minds who found a way to obtain the image deserve our congratulations.</p>



<p>Only half a century ago, black holes were considered, in the words of Italian physicist Carlo Rovelli, &#8220;the barely credible predictions of an esoteric theory.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../black-hole-image-is-beautiful-and-profound-but-it-doesnt-tell-us-much/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 13 Launch Event Set for September 14: How to Watch, What to Expect</title>
		<link>./../../../iphone-13-launch-event-set-for-september-14-how-to-watch-what-to-expect/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../iphone-13-launch-event-set-for-september-14-how-to-watch-what-to-expect/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sirazkhan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 02:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Tech news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=701</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[iPhone 13 launch event is set to be held by Apple on September 14. The invite for a virtual ‘California Streaming&#8217; event has been sent out to the media and a handful of leaks give us an idea of what devices could be launched. The iPhone 13 range is largely anticipated to be announced at &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="./../../../iphone-13-launch-event-set-for-september-14-how-to-watch-what-to-expect/index.html"> <span class="screen-reader-text">iPhone 13 Launch Event Set for September 14: How to Watch, What to Expect</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>iPhone 13 launch event is set to be held by Apple on September 14. The invite for a virtual ‘California Streaming&#8217; event has been sent out to the media and a handful of leaks give us an idea of what devices could be launched. The iPhone 13 range is largely anticipated to be announced at the event, alongside the Apple Watch Series 7 smartwatch. Even the third generation AirPods are likely to be unveiled on Tuesday. The iPhone 13 range is likely to include four models – iPhone 13 mini, iPhone 13, iPhone 13 Pro, and iPhone 13 Pro Max.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../iphone-13-launch-event-set-for-september-14-how-to-watch-what-to-expect/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HBO Max India Plans Leaked Ahead of Official Launch, May Start at Rs. 69 per Month</title>
		<link>./../../../hbo-max-india-plans-leaked-ahead-of-official-launch-may-start-at-rs-69-per-month/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../hbo-max-india-plans-leaked-ahead-of-official-launch-may-start-at-rs-69-per-month/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sirazkhan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 00:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Tech news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=618</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[HBO Max, the over-the-top (OTT) streaming service that specifically offers HBO content alongside originals, TV shows, and Hollywood movies, is likely to enter India soon. While the exact launch details are yet to be revealed, HBO Max&#8217;s plan details for the Indian market have surfaced online. The streaming service is said to be available in &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="./../../../hbo-max-india-plans-leaked-ahead-of-official-launch-may-start-at-rs-69-per-month/index.html"> <span class="screen-reader-text">HBO Max India Plans Leaked Ahead of Official Launch, May Start at Rs. 69 per Month</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>HBO Max, the over-the-top (OTT) streaming service that specifically offers HBO content alongside originals, TV shows, and Hollywood movies, is likely to enter India soon. While the exact launch details are yet to be revealed, HBO Max&#8217;s plan details for the Indian market have surfaced online. The streaming service is said to be available in three different tiers, starting at Rs. 69 per month. HBO Max would compete against the likes of Amazon Prime Video, Disney+ Hotstar, and Netflix that are already available in the country with catalogues offering international and local content.</p>



<p>Telecom-focussed site OnlyTech has&nbsp;<a href="https://onlytech.com/exclusive-hbo-max-plan-details-leaked-ahead-of-indian-launch/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">reported</a>&nbsp;the India plan details of&nbsp;<a href="https://gadgets.ndtv.com/tags/hbo-max">HBO Max</a>. The plans are said to be shared among a group of users under an online pre-launch survey conducted by market research firm Nepa.</p>



<p>[<strong>Update, September 8, 9:30am:</strong>&nbsp;HBO Max confirmed that it carried out this survey, but said that it doesn&#8217;t indicate what the final plans will be. A spokesperson told Gadgets 360, “We routinely conduct market research with consumers in countries around the world that test a wide range of possible offers and price points for our services. Those being reported that suggest a future launch of HBO Max in India are amongst many being tested and evaluated and do not reflect any current plans.”]</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../hbo-max-india-plans-leaked-ahead-of-official-launch-may-start-at-rs-69-per-month/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do Aliens Exist? Here’s What a NASA Scientist Has to Say About It</title>
		<link>./../../../do-aliens-exist-heres-what-a-nasa-scientist-has-to-say-about-it/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../do-aliens-exist-heres-what-a-nasa-scientist-has-to-say-about-it/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sirazkhan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 00:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Tech news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=612</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The eternal question lurking in the minds of every space enthusiast is — does life exist outside Earth? Despite numerous space expeditions, we have been unable to find any trace of life outside our planet so far. However, every once in a while we hear about a UFO seen in some part of the world. &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="./../../../do-aliens-exist-heres-what-a-nasa-scientist-has-to-say-about-it/index.html"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Do Aliens Exist? Here’s What a NASA Scientist Has to Say About It</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The eternal question lurking in the minds of every space enthusiast is — does life exist outside Earth? Despite numerous space expeditions, we have been unable to find any trace of life outside our planet so far. However, every once in a while we hear about a UFO seen in some part of the world. Most of the time, these sightings turn out to be false alarms. And others remain a mystery. Considering that the universe is infinite, we have barely scratched the surface. So the possibility of finding extraterrestrial life is wide open. A NASA scientist has tried to address questions about aliens and whether they exist.</p>



<p>In a video on&nbsp;<a href="https://gadgets.ndtv.com/tags/nasa">NASA&#8217;s</a>&nbsp;Instagram page, Dr. Lindsay Hays, an astrobiology expert, says this is a really interesting question — one that scientists have been trying to understand and explore for a really long time. Still, they have not been able to discover life on any other planet.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../do-aliens-exist-heres-what-a-nasa-scientist-has-to-say-about-it/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
