<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cryptocurrency &#8211; Future Code Tech</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 02:36:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Doesn&#8217;t Make a Great Deal of Sense: Billionaire Investor Lee Cooperman</title>
		<link>./../../../bitcoin-doesnt-make-a-great-deal-of-sense-billionaire-investor-lee-cooperman/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../bitcoin-doesnt-make-a-great-deal-of-sense-billionaire-investor-lee-cooperman/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sirazkhan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=698</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency has been growing rapidly over the past year, but many investors are yet not sure about it. One of them is Lee Cooperman. The US billionaire investor and hedge fund manager says he still does not understand Bitcoin. Speaking to CNBC, he stopped just short of criticising Bitcoin, saying only that people his age &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="./../../../bitcoin-doesnt-make-a-great-deal-of-sense-billionaire-investor-lee-cooperman/index.html"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Bitcoin Doesn&#8217;t Make a Great Deal of Sense: Billionaire Investor Lee Cooperman</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Cryptocurrency has been growing rapidly over the past year, but many investors are yet not sure about it. One of them is Lee Cooperman. The US billionaire investor and hedge fund manager says he still does not understand Bitcoin. Speaking to CNBC, he stopped just short of criticising Bitcoin, saying only that people his age are finding it difficult to understand the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency. He made it clear that he thinks it&#8217;s not in the interest of the US government to further a substitute for the dollar.</p>



<p>“I have great respect for [media mogul] Barry Diller. And I think he was online recently and I think that he said that&nbsp;<a href="https://gadgets.ndtv.com/tags/bitcoin">Bitcoin</a>&nbsp;was a ‘con job&#8217;. I don&#8217;t know if this is a con job, but I take the easy way out. I say: ‘If you don&#8217;t understand Bitcoin, it means you&#8217;re old. I&#8217;m 78. I&#8217;m old. I don&#8217;t understand it,” Cooperman said during an interview. He added that Bitcoin “does not make a great deal of sense” and he would be very careful in dealing with it.</p>



<p>The chairman of Omega Advisors, a New York-based investment advisory firm, also appeared unsure about the prospects of Bitcoin to become a global currency, asserting it was not in US interest to promote an alternative to the American dollar. He said if people are nervous about the trajectory the world is following and want to save money for the future, then gold should be their preferred choice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../bitcoin-doesnt-make-a-great-deal-of-sense-billionaire-investor-lee-cooperman/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu vs Dogecoin: How Have the Cryptocurrencies Fared in the Past Month?</title>
		<link>./../../../shiba-inu-vs-dogecoin-how-have-the-cryptocurrencies-fared-in-the-past-month/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../shiba-inu-vs-dogecoin-how-have-the-cryptocurrencies-fared-in-the-past-month/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sirazkhan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 00:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=615</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu, the cryptocurrency which made its debut last year, shares some similarities with Dogecoin, including the fact that they are both based on popular memes. But those similarities did not stop SHIB from billing itself in the crypto market as “Dogecoin killer.” It has been somewhat successful in stealing the thunder from Dogecoin, but &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="./../../../shiba-inu-vs-dogecoin-how-have-the-cryptocurrencies-fared-in-the-past-month/index.html"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Shiba Inu vs Dogecoin: How Have the Cryptocurrencies Fared in the Past Month?</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Shiba Inu, the cryptocurrency which made its debut last year, shares some similarities with Dogecoin, including the fact that they are both based on popular memes. But those similarities did not stop SHIB from billing itself in the crypto market as “Dogecoin killer.” It has been somewhat successful in stealing the thunder from Dogecoin, but it does not appear to have made a big dent yet. Trading at a fraction of a penny, it is far behind Dogecoin, which was trading at $0.24 (roughly Rs. 18) Saturday morning (September 11), according to CoinMarketCap.</p>



<p>The&nbsp;<a href="https://pricee.com/api/redirect/t.php?from=gadgets360&amp;redirect=https%3A%2F%2Fcoinmarketcap.com%2Fcurrencies%2Fshiba-inu%2F">market research website&#8217;s data</a>&nbsp;showed that&nbsp;<a href="https://gadgets.ndtv.com/tags/shiba-inu">SHIB</a>&nbsp;has been highly volatile over the past one month. It remained above $0.0000080 (roughly Rs. 0.00059) until August 25 and then began sliding, hitting a bottom of $0.0000056 (roughly Rs. 0.00041) by September 8. It recovered from that low and is now trading around $0.0000070 (roughly Rs 0.00051). Check out the current&nbsp;<a href="https://gadgets.ndtv.com/finance/shiba-inu-price-in-india-today-inr">Shiba Inu Price in India here</a>.</p>



<p>In comparison,&nbsp;<a href="https://gadgets.ndtv.com/tags/dogecoin">DOGE</a>&nbsp;had hit a high of $0.35 (roughly Rs. 25.73) on August 16. For a week after that, it remained above the $0.30 (roughly Rs. 22.060) mark and slid below it on August 24. Dogecoin began losing value earlier this week, coinciding with<a href="https://gadgets.ndtv.com/cryptocurrency/news/bitcoin-price-el-salvador-cryptocurrency-president-nayib-bukele-400-btc-buy-own-200-tranches-2532270">&nbsp;El Salvador&#8217;s adoption of Bitcoin</a>&nbsp;as legal tender and the hiccups the rollout faced. As of September 11 (1:15pm IST),&nbsp;<a href="https://gadgets.ndtv.com/finance/dogecoin-price-in-india-today-inr">Dogecoin price in India</a>&nbsp;stood at Rs. 19.9.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../shiba-inu-vs-dogecoin-how-have-the-cryptocurrencies-fared-in-the-past-month/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
